chargesmart.com 2013-03-27

# 

Thirty years ago, VeriFone introduced the first check verification and credit authorization device ever utilized by merchants in a commercial setting. Since then, VeriFone has grown to become a global leader in secure electronic payment solutions. From the beginning, we have been guided by our commitment to ethics in how our employees interact with each other and how we treat our customers, suppliers and partners.

VeriFone maintains a strict [code of business conduct and ethics](http://ir.verifone.com/phoenix.zhtml?c=187628&p=irol-govConduct) \- a set of legal and ethical principles that strive to maintain the highest ethical standards wherever VeriFone operates. VeriFone's commitment to its code of ethics starts at the top: directors, executives, employees and consultants are all responsible for being familiar with the code and abiding by it. The code also covers subsidiaries and affiliates of VeriFone. We understand that ethical behavior is an individual responsibility and no code can capture every possible ethical or legal situation, which is why we insist that sound judgment and discretion also be exercised.

We need and encourage all of our employees, customers, suppliers and partners to work with us in upholding the principles in our code. If you have any concerns about questionable or inappropriate behavior, please do not hesitate to report it so we can work to resolve the issue immediately. VeriFone has established a [compliance line](https://www.compliance-helpline.com/verifone.jsp), a simple and effective way to express concerns regarding any potentially unethical situation involving VeriFone.

## Compliance Line

VeriFone has established a Compliance Line, a simple, effective way to express concerns regarding any potentially unethical situation involving VeriFone.  
View the Complete Compliance Line Details

## Standard Terms and Conditions

The following document covers the terms and conditions for purchases and purchase orders submitted to VeriFone.  
Complete Terms and Conditions - USA   
Complete Terms and Conditions - Canada

## Privacy Policy

This document was last updated August 26, 2011.

VeriFone, Inc. and its subsidiaries (collectively "VeriFone" or the "company") are sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet. The company believes it is important that you know how it treats the information it receives about you on the Internet.

## Scope

This Privacy Policy covers only data collected through the company's website at www.verifone.com, and any pages linked therefrom that are controlled by the company (collectively the "website") and not any other data collection or processing, including, without limitation, data collection practices of other web pages to which the company links or data that the company or its affiliates collect offline or through web sites that do not display a direct link to this Privacy Policy. Occasionally, the company may refer to this statement in notices and consent requests related to surveys and special-purpose web pages, for example, the company's Careers web pages; under such circumstances, this Privacy Policy applies as modified in the particular notice or consent request (e.g., with respect to types of data collected or purposes of collection).

VeriFone's Safe Harbor Certification covers offline and human resources data, but not data submitted through the website, as further explained in VeriFone's General EEA Safe Harbor Notice . Some of VeriFone's business units and web pages apply this statement subject to specifically disclosed modifications, supplements or exceptions.

## Scope

In general, you can visit the website without telling the company who you are or revealing any information about yourself. VeriFone's Web servers collect the domain names, not the e-mail addresses of visitors. This information is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, etc. VeriFone may use this information to measure the content of its Web site and improve its use.

There are times, however, when VeriFone will need information from you such as your name and address. You will be notified at the time of collection how the company will use the information. Usually, the personal information VeriFone collects is used only by the company to respond to your inquiry, process an order or allow you to access specific account information.

VeriFone will disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on VeriFone or its website, or (b) protect and defend the rights or property of VeriFone and its website.

A technology called cookies may be used to provide you with custom information about VeriFone's products or services. A cookie is a tiny element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so VeriFone can recognize you upon your return. You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie.

At times VeriFone may conduct online surveys to better understand the needs and profile of its visitors. When VeriFone conducts a survey, it will try to let you know how the information will be used at the time of collection.

VeriFone's website may contain links to third-party sites. While VeriFone tries to link only to sites that share its high standards and respect for privacy, the company is not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.

VeriFone will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of this privacy statement.

## Legal Notice

Copyright 2011, All rights reserved. VeriFone, the VeriFone logo, NURIT, Omni, PAYware, Secura, SoftPay, Tranz, Verix, VeriShield, Vx, VeriCentre and Xplorer are either trademarks or registered trademarks of VeriFone in the United States and/or other countries. The absence of a product or service name or logo from this list does not constitute a waiver of VeriFone's trademark or other intellectual property rights concerning that name or logo. All other trademarks or brand names are the properties of their respective holders. All features and specifications about VeriFone products and services are subject to change without notice.

VeriFone, Inc.  
Attn: Legal Department  
2099 Gateway Place, Suite 600  
San Jose, CA 95110-1093  
Fax: (408) 232-7841
